[{"answer": "Well, I feel a lot better tonight than I did after South Carolina, Piers.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "How do you think things have played out since we last spoke?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Well, I'm a big fan of Mitt Romney, not because of his combativeness, but because of his intellect and his ability to persuade all kinds of people to get together and get the right answers.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Was that the kind of Mitt Romney you've been looking for?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "I think that Newt is going to go all the way to the end, the way he says he's going to go all the way to the end.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "But what does that tell you about the way his campaign is now going?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Look, Mitt Romney's big issue is connecting, is being comfortable in his own skin, is to let people know who he really is.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "And we're already seeing him developing into a much more formidable opponent, I would argue, from the debates last week than he may have been if he'd won South Carolina and already won the nomination?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Finally, he did it.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "That's the American way, isn't it?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Well, look, that's what's always said in the primary, Piers.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "It's all good fodder for the opposition as well, isn't it?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Well, we have a very tepid recovery, but we do have a recovery.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "And Jack, what is the truth about the state of the American economy right now, do you think?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "It's not all --", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "What about this?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "So what you're basically saying, Suzy, is that Mitt Romney's inability to sing could become an electoral positive for him?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "Piers, let's get this straight.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Why should do you feel that he should pull out?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "I think it's good if they end up being strong supporters and believers in whoever the winning candidate is.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Is it good for the party if Rick Santorum and Ron Paul continue to the bitter end or should one of them take one for the team fairly soon?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "We felt the same way.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "How did you come across this extra bit of a tape?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "This is the box and the tape is in it.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "And this actually the box you found the tape in, right?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Let me go to Douglas Brinkley here.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "You know, how did we get from A to B?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Well, it's a fascinating story.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "How significant, do you think, these tapes are in terms of suddenly surfacing like this?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Well, that's right.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "What does that tell you?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "Well, you can't write about the Kennedy assassination without grappling with the contents of this tape, meaning the information that's now available on it.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "What is the worth, Douglas, would you say, from an historical important point of view?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "I just saw it on your show.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "How do you know?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Because it wouldn't just be in somebody's box in their estate.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "How do you know he wasn't told to hide it?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Do you believe in any conspiracy theories?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "I think it's fun to do.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "None of them?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "The truth for me is I'm always marketing.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Isn't it, all the Republican race?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Do you talk about it on your stand-up?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Wasn't -- you mean, years ago, they couldn't say Peter?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Why is that Peter?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "That's old English for Ned.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Why are you called Howie?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "So here is a guy who has one of the world's most infamous germaphobias, right?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "You can try.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "Let me -- can I set the record straight?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Do you know who he is?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "But it's great television because it's awkward and uncomfortable.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "He wouldn't get past first go, would he?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "You know what, I'll be totally honest, I loved working with you much more than you loved working with me.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "How are you feeling about Howard Stern replacing me?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "No, I don't think that's our job.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Would you like him to?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "I don't have a lot of followers, because I can't plug -- @HowieMMandel.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "How many followers do you have?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "Because I'm wonderfully entertaining.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "Why would anybody want to follow you?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "You told me to do it.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "Who told you about twitter?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "I would like you to apologize.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "Is that why you called me here today?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "Say sorry for being so annoying.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "For being me?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "We have to -- and this is -- I don't know.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "But what happens to the 30 million people without jobs?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "You can do serious.", "docId": "120130pmt", "aSentId": 733, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 732}]